pinkmonkey.com 2019-03-03

# PinkMonkey.com - Over 350 Free Literature Notes, Literature Classics, Study Guides, Online Textbooks.

**  
PinkMonkey.com Privacy Statement**

**

** Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**  
  
PinkMonkey.com is in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), which became effective April 21, 2000.

 **In compliance with the Childrens Online Protection Act, 15 U.S.C. section 6501 - 6506 and 16 C.F.R.312.1-312.12, this site does not permit children under 13 years of age to become users. If you are under the age of 13, you must ask your parent or guardian to access the site.**

PinkMonkey.com is also in compliance with the initiative and spirit of the guidelines set forth by the [Children's Advertising Review Unit](http://www.caru.org/) (CARU). We have made appropriate changes to our site to ensure compliance even though this is a voluntary action. We considered it a primary goal to remain a "G" rated site. We make every attempt to exclude content that is adult in language or content or contains sexual innuendo. Other teen and student targeted sites view this type of material as an attraction and we do not want to be included in that group. If you find objectionable material on this site or on a site for which we have provided an external link, please let us know [support@pinkmonkey.com](mailto:support@pinkmonkey.com).

**Access to the Internet:** The PinkMonkey.com website is only available to persons with access to the Internet. To reach the site, you must have the proper equipment and connecting devices. The overall Internet contains websites containing material which is not appropriate for all viewers, particularly minors. PinkMonkey recommends that each parent take responsibility for the activity of their children to install effective filtering/blocking mechanisms on each computer a child may access to protect your children from inappropriate content. If you install an effective means of filtering/blocking on each computer, you greatly reduce the ability of your children to access inappropriate content. 

**Contact Information:**

**Information Collected:**

PinkMonkey.com may log referring websites in our system logs for internal tracking purposes. This information is limited to the the URL of the referring link that sent you to the site. In addition, your computer may identify information about your web browser and version, color depth and resolution, operating system version, various web browser plug-ins, IP address, and various other information. No personal information is ever recorded or used. **  
**  
**Use of the Information:**

PinkMonkey.com will never distribute any collected information to any third party. Any information collected is used internally for assisting in the demographic targeting of our content and other internal use. 

**Advertisements:**

PinkMonkey.com is advertiser supported. Some third-party advertisments may ask for your disclosure of personal information and/or participation. Please keep in mind that your participation in these offers and/or advertisements is at your own risk and not a requirement for use of this site.  

**Use of the site:**

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, no person under 13 years of age may use this site. If you are under 13 years of age, you must have an adult parent or guardian access the site. Under no condition are you allowed to register or make use of the PinkMonkey.com website(s) or provide any personal information.

**Cookies:**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

**Choices about Cookies** : You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject all cookies, you may not have access to certain aspects or functions of the website. 

**Practices Regarding Cookies** :  
PinkMonkey may use these cookies for a number of purposes, including: User registration, providing customized content, to keep track of preferences you specify while you are using PinkMonkey's services, Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic, and to improve PinkMonkey's content and services.

**Third Party Cookies on PinkMonkey:**  
Please note that PinkMonkey.com may use other companies to present advertisements on some of our pages and they may set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertiser's use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the PinkMonkey.com Privacy Policy. ****PinkMonkey.com works with third parties that serve ads to this site. To find out more about how Burst! Media manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:[Burst! Media](http://www.burstmedia.com/release/about.asp?gotopage=privacy). To find out more about how Fastclick manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:[Fastclick](http://fastclick.com/company/privacy.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Third-Party Web Beacons:**  
We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo, [click here](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html).

 **Deletion of Account:**

PinkMonkey.com does not require registration for use of the site. No accounts are available.

**
